delivery.net 2004-12-11

# Digital Impact | Privacy Policy

|   
  
---  
|   |  |  |  |   |   
|   |  |   
|   |  Internet user privacy is of paramount importance to Digital Impact and our clients. We support the protection of client and consumers' privacy rights as a fundamental element of our business. 

Respect for customer privacy is the core value of permission-based marketing. Far from limiting the marketer's options, the boundaries of privacy establish a space of opportunity, if obeyed. Messages that remain in accord with these boundaries will frequently find receptive customers. Digital Impact's rigorous permission-based privacy policy is designed to ensure that visitors to our website understand how and why Digital Impact may collect and use information provided by users. 

We support the Fair Information Practice Principles of Notice, Choice, Access, and Security. The following document thoroughly explains our privacy policy. Please read it carefully. If you have any questions, please contact [privacy@digitalimpact.com](mailto:privacy@digitalimpact.com). 

eMarketing Dashboard   
This Digital Impact web site includes a link to eMarketing Dashboard, a password-protected, clients-only section of this site, www.digitalimpact.com. eMarketing Dashboard is not a public web site and is not a consumer site. It is a trademarked, web-based application available only to Digital Impact clients. A client only has access to this part of the web site if the client has purchased our services and received a user name and password from Digital Impact. An additional privacy policy specifically addressing privacy issues related to eMarketing Dashboard is posted within the site and is accessible from a link on the homepage of eMarketing Dashboard. The [TRUSTe](http://www.truste.org/watchdog.html) license does not cover the eMarketing Dashboard. If you are a client and would like to set up an eMarketing Dashboard account, or have problems logging on, please contact your Digital Impact account manager. If you are not yet a client, please click here for more information.   
  
IMPACT, Campaign Manager   
Digital Impact sells IMPACT, an ASP email marketing automation and analysis product individually and as part of its full service offerings. Clients can access IMPACT's Campaign Manager module via the web at https://campaignmanager.digitalimpact.net. A client only has access to this web site if the client has purchased our services and received a user name and password from Digital Impact. The TRUSTe license does not cover IMPACT or the Campaign Manager module of IMPACT. If you are a client interested in IMPACT or you are having problems logging on, please contact Digital Impact Account Manager or Technical Support. If you are not yet a client, please click here for more information.   
  
Compliance   
  
TRUSTe   
[](https://www.truste.org/ivalidate.php?url=www.digitalimpact.com)Digital Impact is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for www.digitalimpact.com. 

TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to build users' trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. For more information on TRUSTe, please click here. Because this web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to users' privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe. By displaying the TRUSTe trustmark, this web site has agreed to notify users of: 

1\. What personally identifiable information of yours is collected through the web site  
2\. The organization collecting the information  
3\. How the information is used  
4\. With whom the information may be shared  
5\. What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information  
6\. The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under Digital Impact's control  
7\. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information

If you feel that this company is not abiding by its posted privacy policy, you should first contact Digital Impact's privacy manager by email at [privacy@digitalimpact.com](mailto:privacy@digitalimpact.com). 

If you do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should then contact TRUSTe. TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison to Digital Impact to resolve your concerns. 

Safe Harbor   
Digital Impact abides by the principles of the Safe Harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union. The Direct Marketing Association (DMA) serves as Digital Impact's third-party dispute resolution provider. 

If you feel that this company is not abiding by its posted privacy policy or is not in compliance with the Safe Harbor principles, you should first contact Digital Impact's privacy manager by email at [privacy@digitalimpact.com](mailto:privacy@digitalimpact.com). 

If you do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should then contact the DMA Safe Harbor Dispute Resolution Program. The DMA will then serve as a liaison to Digital Impact to resolve your concerns. 

You can reach the DMA Safe Harbor Program at [safeharbor@the-dma.org](mailto:safeharbor@the-dma.org), or if you prefer to send mail or call: 

Mail:  
Safe Harbor Line  
Direct Marketing Association  
1111 19th Street, NW - Suite 1100  
Washington, DC 20036  
Phone: 202.861.2445 

Information Collection And Use   
  
Digital Impact is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Digital Impact collects information from our users at several different points on our website. Newsletters/Email Alert Services   
If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. Digital Impact uses the information provided to fulfill a user's request for information and personalize the newsletter for the user. To subscribe to the Investors Relations email alerts, a user must provide their email address. Surveys   
From time-to-time, our site may request information from users via surveys. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary, so the user has a choice whether or not to disclose the information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and email address), and demographic information (such as zip code, occupation). Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. Resume Submissions   
Located under "Jobs," a user may submit their resume online. The user is required to provide their name and email address along with a resume. The information is used to screen candidates and contact them for interviews. Cookies   
Digital Impact uses cookies for the sole purpose of tailoring web content to match the user's browser capability. These cookies do not store personal information. 

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. 

Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). Digital Impact has no access to or control over these cookies. 

Sensors   
Digital Impact does not use sensors on this website. 

In order to determine a recipient's ability to receive HTML-based email messages, Digital Impact includes a coded sensor in all of its HTML-based email messages. The sensor activates when the email message is opened and flags the email address of the recipient as one that is capable of receiving HTML-based email messages. 

This capability helps us to send the e-mail in a format you can read, to allow us to track the aggregate number of e-mails read and to measure in aggregate if any of the links in the e-mail were accessed. No other information is collected or used by the sensor. If the recipient cannot receive HTML, the recipient will not receive a functioning sensor. 

Log Files   
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. Sharing   
We may partner with third parties to provide specific services related to information on Investors Relations and Career Opportunities. When the user signs up for these services, we will share contact information, such as email address, which is necessary for the third party to provide these services. A third party contractor may review resumes for screening purposes. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services. 

We may share aggregated demographic information with our partners. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. 

Links   
We use email links located on the "Contact Us" page and the "Resume Submission" page to allow users to contact us directly with any questions or comments they may have. We read every message sent in and try to reply promptly. We use the information collected to respond directly to your questions or comments. We may also file user comments to improve the site and program, or review and discard the information. Users' personal information is only shared with third parties to fulfill service requests made by the user and in the situations described above. 

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Digital Impact is not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Digital Impact. 

Security   
We do not request sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number) from our users. 

Digital Impact takes every precaution to protect our users' information both online and offline. 

Periodically, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our customers' information is protected. The servers on which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment, behind a locked cage. 

If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send an email to [privacy@digitalimpact.com](mailto:privacy@digitalimpact.com). 

Special Offers   
We send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Confirmed members will occasionally receive information on products, services, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Please see our choice and opt-out below. Please see the section below on choice/opt-out. Site and Service Updates   
We communicate with the user to provide requested services and respond to information requests via email or phone. Correction/Updating Personal Information:   
If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data provided to us. A user can update personal information and preferences at the member information and preferences page, which can be accessed by clicking on the link within the email the user receives, clicking on the link to the newsletter located on the home page or contacting us through the link on our website. Users can also send a request to Director of Privacy, Digital Impact, 177 Bovet Road, San Mateo, CA 94402. We will respond to requests within thirty days Choice/Opt-out   
Only users who sign up to receive communications from Digital Impact will receive email from Digital Impact. Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or email alerts from Digital Impact may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying with unsubscribe in the subject line in the email, by clicking on the link within the email the user receives, clicking on the link to the newsletter located on the home page, contacting us through the link on our website or emailing us at [postmaster@digitalimpact.com](mailto:postmaster@digitalimpact.com). 

Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or email alerts from Digital Impact may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying with unsubscribe in the subject line in the email or emailing us at [postmaster@digitalimpact.com](mailto:postmaster@digitalimpact.com). 

NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES   
  
This policy was last revised in December 2002. Our methods of information collection and uses of the information are unchanged. Revisions were limited to: addition of description of IMPACT and an update of the description of the services we provide to our clients. 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we would notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. 

DIGITAL IMPACT CLIENTS   
  
Digital Impact works with the world's leading marketers to create permission-based email marketing programs that achieve superior results. 

Digital Impact's role in supporting our clients may include hosting the actual collection site, delivery of email, tracking results of email campaigns, analysis of data, and transferring collected data back to the client. Digital Impact is contractually bound to keep our clients' customer data private and this data is never shared across clients. 

Digital Impact provides both full service marketing solutions (utilizing our ASP product internally) and email marketing ASP products to its clients. For all clients (full-service and self-service), Digital Impact has a strict policy against sending unsolicited commercial email. If problems arise with a client's campaign, Digital Impact will work with the client to resolve the problems and prevent them in the future. If Digital Impact determines that a client has knowingly used our system for sending unsolicited commercial email, Digital Impact will revoke the right of this client to send email using our product and sending email from our system. 

In addition to sending sophisticated email campaigns on behalf of clients, Digital Impact also provides web page-hosting services and a website tracking and analysis service. Some clients use all of our services. Some clients only use our technology to send email campaigns. Providing these services, Digital Impact acts as a service provider for our clients. This means that Digital Impact is a third party that processes data only on behalf of our clients for the completion of stated purposes. The client, not Digital Impact, owns data collected by Digital Impact on behalf of the client. 

This privacy policy only covers this website - www.digitalimpact.com \- and the information collected through this website. 

Digital Impact may collect information for a client from the emails sent on behalf of the client to its customers. At a client's request, Digital Impact may also collect information for a client from its website. For more information on how Digital Impact supports clients in their email marketing efforts, you may wish to refer to Digital Impact's P3P Privacy Summary. 

Digital Impact's P3P Privacy Summary provides descriptions of information collection activities performed by Digital Impact on behalf of our clients using our email marketing ASP products. The summary also addresses information collected on client websites by Digital Impact on behalf of clients using Digital Impact's web page-hosting services and/or website tracking and analysis service.   
  
---|---  
|   |
